Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
(Episode 12)
(الحلقة 12)
Weren't you quite brave that day?
ألم تكن شجاعًا تمامًا في ذلك اليوم؟
You fought back.
لقد قاومت.
This is different.
هذا مختلف.
Look, it's so cruel.
انظر، إنه أمر قاسٍ جدًا.
Hurry up.
اسرع.
Are you trying to kill me?
هل تحاول قتلي؟
I don't know how to do this!
لا أعرف كيف أفعل هذا!
Let me teach you.
دعني أعلمك.
You have to pay tuition for this.
يجب عليك دفع الرسوم الدراسية لهذا.
So there are things you're afraid of too.
لذا هناك أشياء تخاف منها أيضًا.
What are you doing? Are you flirting here?
ماذا تفعل؟ هل تغازل هنا؟
Hurry up. Crazy people.
اسرعوا. أيها المجانين.
Why don't I do it?
لماذا لا أفعل ذلك؟
Okay.
تمام.
You're really weird.
أنت غريب حقا.
Logically speaking, you're part of the Tong family now.
منطقيا، أنت جزء من عائلة تونغ الآن.
But you're still delivering fish.
لكنك لا تزال تقوم بتوصيل الأسماك.
Have you thought about going back...
هل فكرت بالعودة...؟
to the Tong family to be the young master again?
إلى عائلة تونغ ليكون السيد الشاب مرة أخرى؟
I'd be lying if I say I haven't thought about it.
سأكون كاذبًا إذا قلت أنني لم أفكر في هذا الأمر.
But I'm used to being free.
لكنني اعتدت على أن أكون حرا.
The people there...
الناس هناك...
are too scary. It doesn't suit me.
مخيفة جدًا. لا تناسبني.
Right.
يمين.
If I were you, I'd make the same choice.
لو كنت مكانك، سأختار نفس الاختيار.
I'm free-spirited and want to be uninhibited.
أنا حر الروح وأريد أن أكون غير مقيد.
You don't know how lucky you are.
أنت لا تعرف مدى حظك.
What if I'm not lucky at all?
ماذا لو لم أكن محظوظا على الإطلاق؟
I guess we won't know that.
أعتقد أننا لن نعرف ذلك.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
You want me to take the initiative for this?
هل تريد مني أن أتخذ المبادرة في هذا الأمر؟
Why did you suddenly ask me out today?
لماذا طلبت مني الخروج فجأة اليوم؟
Is it about work?
هل يتعلق الأمر بالعمل؟
Is work the only way...
هل العمل هو السبيل الوحيد...؟
you and I can see each other?
هل يمكننا أن نرى بعضنا البعض؟
Da Huan.
دا هوان.
Don't stress yourself out.
لا تضغط على نفسك.
I'll take care of the merger.
سأعتني بالاندماج.
I'll give you a solid foothold in the Legal Department.
سأعطيك موطئ قدم قوي في القسم القانوني.
Thank you, Yu Chen.
شكرا لك، يو تشن.
There are indeed many things I don't yet understand.
هناك بالفعل العديد من الأشياء التي لم أفهمها بعد.
Don't be too nervous.
لا تكن متوتراً جداً.
Do you remember...
هل تذكر...
our club's social gathering?
التجمع الاجتماعي لنادينا؟
You were forced to sing three songs.
لقد أجبرت على غناء ثلاث أغاني.
Did you know?
هل تعلم؟
The guys were going crazy over you...
لقد كان الرجال يجنون من أجلك...
and discussing you behind your back.
ومناقشة أمرك خلف ظهرك.
That's when I noticed you.
حينها لاحظتك.
Don't bring that up.
لا تذكر هذا .
It was so awkward.
لقد كان الأمر محرجًا جدًا.
I remember after the performance,
أتذكر بعد الأداء،
I lost a necklace.
لقد فقدت قلادة.
I know about that.
انا أعلم ذلك.
You were looking for it backstage and asked me about it.
لقد كنت تبحث عنه خلف الكواليس وسألتني عنه.
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
You helped me look for it for a long time.
لقد ساعدتني في البحث عنه لفترة طويلة.
But I didn't manage to find it in the end.
ولكنني لم أتمكن من العثور عليه في النهاية.
Out with the old, in with the new.
الخروج مع القديم، الدخول مع الجديد.
Speaking of which,
وبالحديث عن ذلك،
I haven't been back to the school in a long time.
لم أعود إلى المدرسة منذ وقت طويل.
Me too.
أنا أيضاً.
Let's go today then.
فلنذهب اليوم إذن.
Okay, I'll go to the restroom first.
حسنًا، سأذهب إلى الحمام أولًا.
We'll go when I'm back.
سنذهب عندما أعود.
Okay.
تمام.
This necklace must be expensive.
لابد أن تكون هذه القلادة باهظة الثمن.
Da Huan never accepts such expensive things.
دا هوان لا يقبل أبدًا مثل هذه الأشياء الباهظة الثمن.
It's you.
إنه أنت.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Can't I give her a present?
ألا يمكنني أن أعطيها هدية؟
Sure, but I'm accepting it on behalf of my sister.
بالتأكيد، ولكنني أقبل ذلك نيابة عن أختي.
After all, Da Huan and I are family.
بعد كل شيء، أنا ودا هوان عائلة.
You're such a busybody.
أنت فضولي للغاية.
You don't have to be polite with me.
لا يتوجب عليك أن تكون مهذبًا معي.
I'll just say one thing.
سأقول شيئا واحدا فقط.
Stay away from Jin Da Huan.
ابتعد عن جين دا هوان.
What era are we in now?
في أي عصر نحن الآن؟
Da Huan should have the right to choose.
ينبغي أن يكون لدى دا هوان الحق في الاختيار.
If you really love her,
إذا كنت تحبها حقا،
you should respect how she really feels.
يجب عليك احترام مشاعرها الحقيقية.
What if she's longing to marry me?
ماذا لو كانت تتوق للزواج مني؟
I don't care what she thinks.
لا يهمني ما تفكر به.
I hope you don't stoop too low.
أتمنى أن لا تنحدر إلى مستوى منخفض للغاية.
Respect her.
احترمها.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
You don't look well.
أنت لا تبدو بخير.
I'm fine. Your brother was here.
أنا بخير. أخوك كان هنا.
Well? You've had a long day.
حسنًا؟ لقد كان يومك طويلًا.
This is nothing.
هذا لا شيء.
Okay, I'll transfer it to you later.
حسنًا، سأنقله إليك لاحقًا.
Let's continue tomorrow.
دعونا نواصل غدا.
Again?
مرة أخرى؟
Are you crazy?
هل انت مجنون؟
I'm willing to.
أنا على استعداد لذلك.
Jin Da Xi.
جين دا شي.
Hand it over.
سلمها.
Hand what over?
تسليم ماذا؟
Are you going to keep pretending?
هل ستستمر بالتظاهر؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Why did you take the thing...
لماذا أخذت هذا الشيء...
that Yu Cheng gave me?
الذي أعطاني إياه يو تشنغ؟
Yes, I told you not to do that.
نعم لقد قلت لك لا تفعل ذلك.
Where did you put it? Give it to her.
أين وضعته؟ أعطها إياه.
Did you leave it in the shop?
هل تركته في المحل؟
Let's go get it now.
دعونا نذهب للحصول عليه الآن.
Da Huan, the situation is a bit unusual.
دا هوان، الوضع غير عادي بعض الشيء.
Let me apologize to you first.
دعني أعتذر لك أولاً.
I'll explain it to you another day.
سأشرح لك ذلك في يوم آخر.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Da Huan, we'll get it back for you right away.
دا هوان، سوف نعيده إليك على الفور.
What era are we in?
في أي عصر نحن؟
Da Huan should have the right to choose.
ينبغي أن يكون لدى دا هوان الحق في الاختيار.
Tong Sheng, what are you looking at?
تونغ شنغ، ما الذي تنظر إليه؟
- Nothing. - Tong Sheng, are you in love?
- لا شيء. - تونغ شنغ، هل أنت في حالة حب؟
Am I going to have a sister-in-law?
هل سيكون لي أخت زوجة؟
The choice is up to the other person.
الاختيار متروك للشخص الآخر.
Is it Ms. Yan?
هل هي السيدة يان؟
I can come and go freely now.
أستطيع أن أذهب وأأتي بحرية الآن.
You don't have to visit me every day.
ليس من الضروري أن تزورني كل يوم.
It's okay. I just like to bring you food.
لا بأس، أنا فقط أحب أن أحضر لك الطعام.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I'll leave it here. I'll get going.
سأترك الأمر هنا. سأذهب.
Your department store has been busy...
لقد كان متجرك مشغولاً...
with the merger and acquisition of Xuebao Group, right?
مع اندماج واستحواذ مجموعة Xuebao، أليس كذلك؟
Yes, and we've been working overtime every night.
نعم، وكنا نعمل لساعات إضافية كل ليلة.
But luckily, we're in the final stage.
ولكن لحسن الحظ أننا في المرحلة النهائية.
Once it is over, we'll be one family.
بمجرد أن ينتهي الأمر، سنكون عائلة واحدة.
Give me a moment.
أعطني لحظة.
The coffee here...
القهوة هنا...
tastes exactly like the one we had at school.
طعمه يشبه تمامًا ما تناولناه في المدرسة.
I remember you loved their coffee.
أتذكر أنك أحببت قهوتهم.
You still remember that?
هل لازلت تتذكر ذلك؟
Da Huan.
دا هوان.
Are you happy being with me?
هل أنت سعيدة بوجودك معي؟
I'm quite happy.
أنا سعيد جدًا.
Then...
ثم...
Then can you accept my gift?
إذن هل يمكنك قبول هديتي؟